Development scene: walking, stops and directional turns.
Development scene: pipe pickup.
Development scene: pipe held walk right stop.
Development scene: pipe held walk left stop.
Development scene: pipe attack and kick.
Development scene: pipe throw land and same node repickup.
Development scene: alley punk approach turn stop.
Development scene: alley punk attack hit recover.
Development scene: biker raider approach turn stop.
Development scene: biker raider attack hit recover.
Development scene: riot grunt approach turn stop.
Development scene: riot grunt attack hit recover.
Development scene: knife runner approach turn stop.
Development scene: knife runner attack hit recover.
Development scene: neon tagger approach turn stop.
Development scene: neon tagger attack hit recover.
Development scene: shock baton thug approach turn stop.
Development scene: shock baton thug attack hit recover.
Development scene: pipe bruiser approach turn stop.
Development scene: pipe bruiser attack hit recover.
Development scene: scrap brute approach turn stop.
Development scene: scrap brute attack hit recover.
Development scene: conductor approach turn stop.
Development scene: conductor attack hit recover.